Guide to the Steffi Domike Papers, 1946-2009 AIS.1997.20
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio/Visual Materials, IX.
  - Out of This Furnace: A Walking Tour of Thomas Bell's Novel, 6.
    This subseries of videocassettes comprises footage taken for the walking tour of Thomas Bell's novel,Out of This Furnace which documents three generations of mill workers in Braddock, Pennsylvania. The film was developed by Steffie Domike and David Demarest. Demarest was responsible for the book's 1976 reissue by the University of Pittsburgh Press and its afterword. Led by Demarest, the viewer is taken on a trip through Braddock using recent footage, commentary, historic photographs, and readings from the novel.
    - Out of This Furnace: A Walking Tour of Thomas Bell's Novel Videos, 9 Betacam, 2 VHS (Box 39, Video 392-403)
  - Steel Valley Authority, 7.
    The Steel Valley Authority was created in 1986 as a coalition of several municipalities in the Mon Valley. Their goal was to revitalize the economic base of the area, including where possible the preservation of its status as a world steel making center. Another goal of the Steel Valley Authority was to explore the possibility of public ownership of abandoned or soon to be abandoned industrial facilities. This subseries contains interviews with several key figures in the Steel Valley Authority, as well as footage of several of the Authority's meetings. The Steel Valley Authority was still active as of 2007 and its main areas of focus include the creation or preservation of industrial jobs, community development, and investing in small to medium sized industrial businesses.
    - Steel Valley Authority Videos, 12 3/4" Umatic (Box 40, Video 404-415)
    - Steel Valley Authority Videos, 12 3/4" Umatic (Box 41, Video 416-427)
    - Steel Valley Authority Videos, 12 3/4" Umatic (Box 42, Video 428-439)
    - Steel Valley Authority Videos, 7 VHS, 7 3/4" Umatic (Box 43, Video 440-453)
  - Assorted Video, 8.
    This subseries contains a large variety of video cassettes regarding such topics as the 1990 Greyhound strike, the United Mine Workers of America, and episodes of Domike's television program, On Camera, which featured independently produced films. There is also plenty of raw footage that feature small projects like promotional videos for United Steelworkers of America, Pennsylvania Department of Education, and other organizations, visual explorations of historical towns, documentation of various events, and tapes made up solely of videoed images. Some of the items in this subseries were not produced or filmed by Domike but were a part of her collection.
    - Balcony 1, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 43, Video 454)
    - Balcony 2 Feeney and Friends auction, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 43, Video 455)
    - Balcony 3 Anne Feeney, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 456)
    - Balcony 4 Feeney, September 29, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 457)
    - Balcony 5, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 458)
    - Balcony 6, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 459)
    - Balcony 7 Pete Seeger and John Handcox, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 460)
    - Balcony 8 Finale, Roll the Union On, If I had a Hammer, Solidarity Forever, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 461)
    - Hazel Dickens Interview - 8, September 30, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 462)
    - Dr. Joe Interview - 9, September 29, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 463)
    - John Handcox Interview - 10, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 464)
    - #1-6 Labor Arts Fest, September 29, 1989; 7 3/4" Umatic (Box 44, Video 465-470)
    - #7 Labor Arts Fest, September 29, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 45, Video 471)
    - Pete Seeger Interview, September 30, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 45, Video 472)
    - Tom Juravich interview, October 1, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 45, Video 473)
    - Shaun Nethercott Interview of Workers' Lives/Workers' Stories, September 30, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 45, Video 474)
    - Balcony #1-10 Graffiti, September 30, 1989; 8 3/4" Umatic (Box 45, Video 475-484)
    - #3-4 Floor Saturday, Workers' Lives/Workers' Stories, September 30, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 46, Video 485-486)
    - What Do We Win? East Liberty - UNO, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 487)
    - What Do We Win? Homestead, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 488)
    - What Do We Win? Homestead #1 and 3 Rivers, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 489)
    - What Do We Win? Squirrel Hill, 1996; 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 490)
    - Dubbed Footage "Who is the We?", 1996; 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 491)
    - Sq. Hill SVHS #5-6, 2 VHS (Box 46, Video 492-493)
    - On Camera #103, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 46, Video 494)
    - On Camera #107, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 495)
    - On Camera #105 and #106, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 496)
    - On Camera #107 and #108 - Experimental and Animations, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 497)
    - On Camera #201, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 498)
    - On Camera #1, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 499)
    - Pioneer Oasis - Old Bedford Village, 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 500)
    - Bedford #1 - Pioneer Historical Society, May 29, 1996; 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 501)
    - Bedford #2 - Old Bedford Village, June 22, 1996; 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 502)
    - Bedford Neg. Xfer Dupe from Beta, December 4, 1995; 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 503)
    - Bedford Negative Transfer, December 1, 1995; 1 Betacam (Box 46, Video 504)
    - Steffi Domike Documentation - "Who is the We?", "John & Sarah", "360°", 1 VHS (Box 46, Video 505)
    - On Camera Special Reel #1-2, 2 Betacam (Box 46, Video 506-507)
    - Sq. Hill SVHS #1-4 Rummykub, Darts, Mahjongg, 4 VHS (Box 47, Video 508-511)
    - Tom Fagan #1-5, February 1, 1988; 5 3/4" Umatic (Box 47, Video 512-516)
    - UMWA #1-4, 4 3/4" Umatic (Box 47, Video 517-20)
    - UMWA #5-10, 6 3/4" Umatic (Box 48, Video 521-526)
    - USWA Hands Across America, May 2, 1986; 1 VHS (Box 48, Video 527)
    - Duquesne Meeting #4, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 48, Video 528)
    - 360° An Urban Ecology Project - Dub from Hi-8, 1 VHS (Box 48, Video 529)
    - 360° - Back alley, April 14, 1996; 1 VHS (Box 48, Video 530)
    - Stephanie, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 48, Video 531)
    - Homestead Destruction, January 17, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 48, Video 532)
    - USWA Rally B Roll, August 29, 1989; 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 533)
    - Camp Solidarity #6 Interviews, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 534)
    - Camp Solidarity #5 Food Delivery, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 535)
    - Camp Solidarity #4 Ron Baker Interview, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 536)
    - Camp Solidarity #3 Breakfast, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 537)
    - Camp Solidarity #2 Musicians, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 538)
    - Camp Solidarity #1 Musicians, 1 Betacam (Box 48, Video 539)
    - #2-4, 3 Betacam (Box 48, Video 540-542)
    - The Business of America Reel 1-2, 2 Betacam (Box 48, Video 543-544)
    - Homestead Reel 1-2, May 4, 1988; 2 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 545-546)
    - Homestead Heritage: Lessons for Tomorrow, January 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 547)
    - Recharge South Side Steel, March 29, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 548)
    - Split Tracks - Forging a Future in Steel, 1991; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 549)
    - H-9, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 550)
    - Deadly Dilemma (Toxics in the workplace), The Bayview Massacre, Snowing in the Tropics, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 551)
    - Health Care Reform TV Spots, 1990; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 552)
    - The Year in Labor VNR, December 26, 1990; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 553)
    - UPERC People Equal to the Task, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 49, Video 556)
    - Homestead Destruction Reel 2, January 17, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 554)
    - Dusquesne - Save Dorothy Meeting #3, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 555)
    - ERA Supporters March, December 28, 1984; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 557)
    - Forging a Future in Steel - Field tape #2, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 558)
    - T-Rex Roll #2 "Duquesne Demolition", January 30, 1995; 1 VHS (Box 50, Video 559)
    - "Duquesne" 1-Lite film transfer, December 4, 1995; 1 VHS (Box 50, Video 560)
    - "Duquesne" A Pictorial History, 1 VHS (Box 50, Video 561)
    - Mon Valley Media "T. Rex" 1-Light transfer, March 30, 1994; 1 VHS (Box 50, Video 562)
    - Tom Dawson, 4 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 563-566)
    - Tyranny Rex sample tape, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 50, Video 567)
    - "Duquesne" 1-Lite film transfer, December 1, 1995; 1 Betacam (Box 50, Video 568)
    - Raw footage Duquesne demo, January 13, 1995; 1 Betacam (Box 50, Video 569)
    - LMC #11 Pittsburgh Skyline, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 570)
    - LMC #9 Thomas Foerster and Airport scenes, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 571)
    - LMC #3 T.J. McGarvey and Paul Stackhouse, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 572)
    - LMC #10 Midfield Terminal Cement Pour, September 7, 1989; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 573)
    - LMC #1 Three Rivers Area Civic, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 574)
    - LMC #2 3 Rivers LMC, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 575)
    - Working Safely: Joint Safety and Health Committees, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 576)
    - Filmmakers of Phila., Inc. Achievement and Challenge, May 1981; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 577)
    - University of Pittsburgh People Equal to the Task - remixed, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 578)
    - Reel #100 MVM, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 579)
    - Misc. Clips from USWA Transfers, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 580)
    - We are the People - Selects of historical clips, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 51, Video 581)
    - Frank O'Brien, 1 VHS (Box 51, Video 582)
    - Steffi Domike's Compilation Tape, 1 VHS (Box 52, Video 583)
    - United Steelworkers of America Reform at Last, 1 VHS (Box 52, Video 584)
    - $4 a Day? No Way! American Labor Education Center, 1 VHS (Box 52, Video 585)
    - Greyhound Protest Arrests, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 586)
    - Greyhound Support Rally from Washington Works, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 587)
    - Archival Footage - Mon Valley Steel Mills, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 588)
    - Labor Management #5 - biology lab Dr. McCall, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 589)
    - Labor Management #9 - CCAC Overviews, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 590)
    - Labor Management #7 - CCAC Library and Thomas Lennox, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 591)
    - Labor Management #6 - campus-Lou's clean exteriors library, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 592)
    - Working Safely: Joint Union Management Safety Committee, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 593)
    - "One Voice" Reel #1-2, 2 Betacam (Box 52, Video 594-595)
    - You Can't Keep a Good Plant Down, 1988; 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 596)
    - "Pioneers", 1990; 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 597)
    - Labor Live Msgr Rice Interview #1-2, September 4, 1990; 2 Betacam (Box 52, Video 598-599)
    - Labor Live Open, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 600)
    - Labor Live Title, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 601)
    - Labor's Corner Open Promo Master tape #3, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 602)
    - Labor's Corner Credits Pittston Rally #2, 1989; 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 603)
    - Labor's Corner #58 Studio Tape, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 604)
    - Labor Day Parade Promo Video, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 605)
    - Labor's Corner Archive P&LE #1 of 3, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 606)
    - Labor's Corner Field tape #1 Pittston March, August 13, 1989; 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 607)
    - Greyhound Bus Station, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 608)
    - UMWA Pittston Rally #2-3, August 13, 1989; 3 Betacam (Box 52, Video 609-611)
    - Labor Live Pilot Greyhound Intro, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 612)
    - Greyhound Narration, 1 Betacam (Box 52, Video 613)
    - "Even the Heavens Weep" Tapes 1-3, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 614-616)
    - "A Turn for the Best", 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 617)
    - "We're All Strangers in This World" master interview channel, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 618)
    - SEIU Dignity master, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 619)
    - Pittsburgh Gnostics 1 of 3, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 620)
    - Steel Sticks N' Stones, 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 621)
    - P.M. Magazine Piston Dispute, 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 622)
    - "Recharge South Side Steel", 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 623)
    - USWA "Caring with a Contract", December 12, 1985; 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 624)
    - Work Worth Doing Part 1 and 2, 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 625)
    - USWA Vidnet - Civil Rights "To Dream", 1 VHS (Box 53, Video 626)
    - Steel Sticks N' Stones red titles, 1996; 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 627)
    - Forging a Future in Steel field tape #1, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 53, Video 628)
    - Media Video Dub Healthcare Video, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 53, Video 629)
    - Leslie Ronder #2, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 53, Video 630)
    - Steel Sticks N' Stones from Toaster, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 631)
    - Paul and Steffi Compilation, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 632)
    - CFE at Clarkbar - Part II of Live feed at Beehive Sound, 1 Betacam (Box 53, Video 633)
    - Health Care: Critical Condition, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 634)
    - USWA Vidnet - "Caring with a Contract", December 15, 1986; 2 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 635-636)
    - "The Fight for our Lives", 1987; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 637)
    - J&L Steel - Heinz 66, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 638)
    - The Canterbury Tale unmixed master, September 13, 1987; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 639)
    - The Canterbury Tale in the coal fields, October 1987; 2 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 640-61)
    - CWA/WRS video dub reel #1-2, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 54, Video 642-643)
    - Trade Secrets, 1 VHS, 1 Betacam (Box 54, Video 644-645)
    - Blakked - Fletcher family flicks, 1 Betacam (Box 54, Video 646)
    - Work Force #1-2, 2 Betacam (Box 54, Video 647-648)
    - Volta Redonda Strike Memorial Iser-Video-Brazil, 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 649)
    - Pittsburgh Working Together, 1989; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 650)
    - Make Your Own Space, April 27, 1987; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 651)
    - The Struggle for an American Way of Life: Coal Miners and Operators in Central PA., 1919-1933; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 652)
    - Safety & Health Music Video "More Than a Paycheck", March 13, 1990; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 653)
    - "Lives of Steel" WTAE CH 4 Through the Years Special, July 19, 1989; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 654)
    - McKeesport Heritage Center Reflections - Part II, 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 655)
    - Pennsylvania Labor History Conference, Homestead, October 4, 2003; 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 656)
    - Steffi Domike's Resume Tape: "Women of Steel," "Caring...with a Contract," and "People Equal to the Task", 1 VHS (Box 55, Video 657)
    - Andrew Carnegie, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 55, Video 658)
    - Make Your Own Space mixed master, April 24, 1987; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 55, Video 659)
    - Space Master "Make Your Own Space", 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 55, Video 660)
    - Alex, May 10, 1988; 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 55, Video 661)
    - Military Spots, 1 3/4" Umatic (Box 55, Video 662)
    - Steffi Domike, 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 663)
    - Penn State J&L Mill Process #3, 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 664)
    - Links in the Chain Slides #1-2, 2 Betacam (Box 56, Video 665-666)
    - Links in the Chain #1-5, 5 Betacam (Box 56, Video 667-671)
    - Clairton Shoot Exteriors, March 1988; 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 672)
    - Poland soundtrack, 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 673)
    - Bearing North Loop #1-3, 3 VHS (Box 56, Video 674-676)
    - Bloodline loop for show, 1997; 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 677)
    - Terminal Time documentation reel, 1999; 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 679)
    - "Bloodline" SVHS loop, Skoki, Poland, 1997; 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 678)
    - Terminal Time raw footage of questions, 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 680)
    - Terminal Time prototype, April 18, 1998; 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 681)
    - Terminal Time prototype print, 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 682)
    - J&L Steel: A New Beginning in Pittsburgh, August 7, 1979; 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 683)
    - Penn State #8 J&L #2, 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 684)
    - Penn State #10-11 J&L #4-5, 2 Betacam (Box 56, Video 685-686)
    - Penn State #7 J&L #1, June 5, 1990; 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 687)
    - Labor Management #8 Thomas Lennox, 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 688)
    - "Monessen & Camping", August 9, 1995; 1 Betacam (Box 56, Video 689)
    - Bullfight and Mumia demo, 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 690)
    - Eyes Loop, 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 691)
    - Weird Bug Movie Loop, 1 VHS (Box 56, Video 692)
    - Building Pittsburgh, 17 Betacam (Box 57, Video 693-709)
    - Mapping the Heap, 1997; 3 VHS, 1 Betacam (Box 57, Video 710-713)
    - Building Pittsburgh edit master, 1 Betacam (Box 57, Video 714)
    - "Memorial Day Massacre of 1937", April 4, 1988; 1 3/4" Tape (Box 58, Video 718)
    - Labor Live, 1 3/4" Tape (Box 58, Video 719)
    - "Pittsburgh: Working Together", 1 3/4" Tape (Box 58, Video 720)
    - "Forging a Future in Steel", July 17, 1991; 1 3/4" Tape (Box 58, Video 721)
    - Interviews on Demolition in Homestead, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 722-723)
    - Demolition Loop, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 724)
    - Mill interviews - Duquesne - Frank Samuels, Samuel Dent, October 10, 1995; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 725)
    - Mill Demolition Homestead, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 726)
    - Interview Homestead Retirees, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 727)
    - RRR Reels Homestead Mill Demo, 1992; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 728)
    - Maria's Story - Dewey Beach, 1991; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 729)
    - Women of Steel exteriors, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 730)
    - Women's group on Jo Elliot, December 10, 1994; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 731)
    - Cooperative Sandino, Pinata de Parcival, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 732)
    - Managua game, San Isidro, July 19, 1989; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 733)
    - 360° Budd/Domike, April 1996; 2 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 734-735)
    - Christmas, 1995; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 736)
    - New Years Interview, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 737)
    - WREE Convention 1990- Angela Davis, May 26, 1990; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 738)
    - Who is the We? - Sue, 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 739)
    - NMR Oral History Joel Tarr, February 13, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 65, Cassette 740)
    - Slag Heap, 7 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 741-747)
    - Lines of Power, March 1997; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 748)
    - Bearing North Installation of the Brew House, July 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 749)
    - Joel Tarr Interview #2, April 10, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 750)
    - What do We Win? Interviews; Mahjongg; Bedford-"Formidable Ridges"; Pioneer Oasis; more, 1996; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 751)
    - Dulles airport, Moscow airport, Soviet Women's Conf., street scenes, street musicians, June 1990; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 752)
    - Russia, 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 753)
    - Moscow trip with Elain Jordan of Tulsa, AZ, June 23, 1990; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 754)
    - Poland, 1997; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 755)
    - Bedford, PA, 1996; 3 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 756-758)
    - Sq. Hill Demo & Narration, 1995; 1 Hi8 (Box 66, Cassette 759)
    - TDV, 1989; 6 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 760-765)
    - Terminal Time Prototype, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 766)
    - Fighter With a Heart, November 7, 1996; 2 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 767-768)
    - Robots Alive, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 769)
    - Terminal Time, 15 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 770-784)
    - USWA #1-3, 3 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 785-787)
    - New Zealand, 3 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 788-790)
    - Kosovo-Chem, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 791)
    - The Richest Man in the World #2, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 792)
    - Austria from plane; WTO-beach, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 793)
    - California, May 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 794)
    - 3 Rivers Stadium, February 11, 2001; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 795)
    - WPA Nature - Cornfields, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 796)
    - Stocks crash/news, 1999; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 797)
    - Falwell footage, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 798)
    - Poland Ads 1930s, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 799)
    - Pumphouse Homestead, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 800)
    - Twin Towers, September 11, 2001; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 801)
    - Beauvoir computers, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 802)
    - Pitt shoot/Labor Party, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 803)
    - China, November 8, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 804)
    - Snow-Pgh Sunset; Demo-March-Pgh, 1999; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 805)
    - Voices: Religion, Cold War/Ref. Japan, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 806)
    - The Richest Man in the World #1, 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 807)
    - Bearing North; Student work; TA for Sturgeon, Bloodline video, 1996-1997; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 808)
    - CA - Boat/Woods, 1998; 1 Hi8 (Box 67, Cassette 809)
  - Assorted Film, 9.
    This subseries holds a number of The River Ran Red color negatives, as well as negatives from projects like "Tyranny Rex" and "Children at War."
    - The River Ran Red Negatives (Box 59, Reel 1-12)
    - The River Ran Red Negatives (Box 60, Reel 13-23)
    - The River Ran Red Negatives (Box 61, Reel 24-31)
    - The River Ran Red Negatives (Box 62, Reel 32-39)
    - "Steffi Domike", August 8, 1995 (Box 63, Reel 40)
    - Riding bus scene (Box 63, Reel 41)
    - Busstop scene (Box 63, Reel 42)
    - Rough cut-Children at War (Box 63, Reel 43)
    - "War" Scotty's Diner & White House (Box 63, Reel 44)
    - Children at War Audio-Rough Cut (Box 63, Reel 45)
    - White House Only (Box 63, Reel 46)
    - School Shoot Color Neg. (Box 63, Reel 47)
    - T. Rex negatives (Box 63, Reel 48)
    - White House #2 (Box 63, Reel 49)
    - "War" Rolls 1 and 2 (Box 63, Reel 50)
    - "War" negative, Scotty's Dinner & White House (Box 63, Reel 51)
    - T-Rex Project, January 27, 1995 (Box 63, Reel 52)
    - "Poverty Draft" Rough Cut Sync (Box 63, Reel 53)
    - "The Poverty Draft" Audio-Bus Stop Scene (Box 63, Reel 54)
    - Bus Scene Plus, June 24, 1986 (Box 63, Reel 55)
    - School Misc. Sound-Talking Footsteps (Box 63, Reel 56)
    - Outtake of Children at War (Box 63, Reel 57)
    - Broken Promises (Box 63, Reel 58)
    - Untitled Color Neg., June 17, 1982 (Box 63, Reel 59)
    - W/P School Shoot (Box 63, Reel 60)
    - "Solidarity Day" Steelworkers (Box 63, Reel 61)
    - On Steps with Uncle Sam (Box 63, Reel 62)
    - The River Ran Red Negatives (Box 64, Reel 63)
    - Moving Mountains (Box 64, Reel 64)
  - Assorted Audio, 10.
    - Carol McCracken, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 1)
    - SMC-Carol McCracken Interview from Videotape, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 2)
    - Fran Bartkowski-Interviews while Pregnant, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 3)
    - Fran Bartkowski, January 30, 1988; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 4)
    - Dub of Fran's Interview after Birth of Jules, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 5)
    - Regina Buckner, August 17, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 6)
    - Donna Jo McDaniels, February 9, 1988; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 7)
    - Doreen Chimnar, January 24, 1988; 2 Audio Cassettes (Box 69, Cassette 8-9)
    - Rachel Naismith, 2 Audio Cassettes (Box 69, Cassette 10-11)
    - SMC Group Interview from Videotape, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 12)
    - "Somewhere in Between" for the Being Mom, Being Single project (Box 69, Cassette 13)
      The majority of the audio cassettes in this subseries are interviews for Life without Father. Some are interviews with steelworkers, mix and stereo tapes for Domike's finished films, or soundtracks.
    - Bill Gaughan, May 4, 1988; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 14)
    - Homestead Demolition, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 15)
    - Monsignor Charles Owen Rice Interview, May 30, 1991; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 16)
    - Sam Papa Interview, February 16, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 17)
    - Frank Lupinacci-CWA, August 12, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 18)
    - Shirley Salata, Carporter, June 30, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 19)
    - Karen Supansic, April 13, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 20)
    - Anne MacLemore, 1987; 1 Audio Cassette (Box 69, Cassette 21)
    - UE Interview with Melvin Womack, Evelyn Bell, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 70, Cassette 22)
    - Babe Fernandez Interview, 1 Audio Cassette (Box 70, Cassette 23)
    - "Steel and Steelworkers" Conference Tapes 1-3, June 24, 1995; 3 Audio Cassette (Box 70, Cassette 24-26)